[indistinct chatter]
[rain splattering]
Ugh, this totally sucks.
[laughs]
We were having a blast
a couple of minutes ago!
-How funny!
-Seriously?
This isn't funny, so shut up!
I don't understand
how we got lost
if Ishimori
was looking at the map.
Yeah, were you not paying
attention or something?
[grunts]
Hey, it's pretty gross
to throw her
under the bus for this,
you know?
-[humming]
-Just sayin'.
It's weird, 'cause we followed
all the signs, right?
[NATSUMI]
Maybe someone messed with 'em.
-[humming]
-[MIKARIN] Wait, you think so?
Listen, everyone.
Let's calm down
and think for a sec.
I'm scared!
I wanna go home!
Mama's gonna be
so worried about me!
-[Momo crying]
-Hm?
[MIKARIN]
So, what do we do now?
-[TONBO] Don't look at me.
-I'll go.
[UKA]
I'll get us back on the trail!
[all gasping]
Wait!
Where are you going?
[sighs]
Crap.
[AYUMI]
Kai?
[indistinct chatter]
SPARKLE 4
HOWEVER DISTANT WE MAY BE
[UKA] Once again,
I'm basically just dead weight.
I wanted to be helpful
to everyone.
But now we're all worse off.
[gasps]
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I'm trying to be
the person I want to be.
[UKA]
Maybe I can't.
Maybe I'm wrong
about all of it.
I got us lost.
What if we can't get back?
[sighs]
[gasps]
It's okay.
Just calm down.
[KAI]
We'll be just fine.
[grunting]
The hell?
Hey!
Ah?
♪
[sighs]
[gasps]
Huh!
This bridge here.
It's on the map.
[gasps]
[groans]
[rain splattering]
-[gasps]
-Wait.
Stay right here, okay?
[running footsteps]
♪
[whimpering]
[indistinct chatter]
♪
-[NAGANO] Ishimori.
-Huh?
Hey, I'm so sorry.
I shouldn't have
blamed you like that.
It's fine.
[sneezes]
Uh-oh, Nagano,
did you already catch a cold?
[NAGANO]
I'll be all right.
Hey, um...Nagano,
you need a towel?
Oh, yeah, that'd be great.
[YASUSHI]
Wait.
So, does that humongous
backpack of hers
have enough stuff
for all of us?
[MIKARIN] Is that why
she brought that giant one?
[YASUSHI]
Yeah, I think so.
That's cool, you know?
Oh, yeah.
-She's really stepping up.
-Should have more than enough.
So feel free to go ahead
and drink as much as you need.
[footfall]
[sighs]
-[KAI] Here.
-Huh?
I bet you're thirsty,
and you gave yours away.
[KAI]
I drank some, but here.
I really shouldn't take it if
you've already started on it.
Not really the time
to be picky.
[KAI]
Just drink it, okay?
[UKA]
Actually, I'm being serious.
I mean, I don't deserve it.
♪
[UKA]
What am I even saying?
Miura's got me all mixed up.
He keeps flipping
between being really nice
and downright cold.
[laughs]
[KAI] You're too tired
to think straight, huh?
♪
[chuckles]
Huh!
[UKA]
How's this happening?
I never dreamt
I'd fall in love.
I was always just looking
at the ground in front of me.
[TONBO] Hey, wasn't
there supposed to be
some kinda "heart
in the sky" thing to look at?
[YASUSHI]
Now's not the time, dude!
[KAI]
Guys, come here and look up.
Ishimori found something cool.
-[MARIN] Oh, yeah?
-[MIKARIN] Whoa!
-I wanna see!
-It does look like a heart!
[NAGANO]
Is it good luck?
[MIKARIN] If you look
at it with your crush,
your wish'll come true!
-[ASUMI] Oh, I see it!
-[TONBO] Go on and make a wish!
[SHIRAISHI]
I don't know what I want!
[SATORU]
It's amazing.
[UKA] Even if it's raining,
I'll still look up.
And wish that
we all get home safely.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
Blue sky.
The rainbow after the storms.
And the warm, golden sunlight
breaking through the clouds.
That's where I am now.
[groans]
So loud.
[KAI]
Tryin' to catch some Zs, here.
[UKA]
It's all so wonderful.
I may get the wrong idea again.
-Huh?
-[whimpering]
[gasps]
♪
-You're my pillow.
-[gasps]
Um, is this really okay?
-Stop talking.
-Okay.
[Kai sighs]
[UKA]
"Nothing comes from it.
Only heartbreak."
I haven't found out exactly
what she meant by that yet,
but I'm bound
to learn eventually.
♪
I was able to accept
those feelings before.
But Miura gave me hope.
I need to just enjoy it
while I can.
[engine whirring]
[UKA]
Thanks, Dad!
Your backpack
really came in handy!
That's great.
So, did you have fun
on your field trip?
Oh, yeah!
[panting]
[UKA]
What a change.
I can be positive
without lying.
And now,
I can't wait to get to school.
[indistinct chatter]
Good morning.
[gasps]
[UKA]
Wait...
what's all that stuff
on my desk?
Is...someone messing with me?
Hey, she's here!
Mornin', Ishimori!
[TAO] Sorry, guess we kinda
covered your whole desk.
But it's not like we talked
to each other about it first.
[MIKARIN] Yeah, we just
all ended up bringing stuff.
[SHIRAISHI] They're meant
to be some little
thank you gifts for yesterday.
If that's cool.
[TAO] We might've gone
a little overboard.
[SHIRAISHI]
Darn it.
Yeah, sorry about that.
It's a little extra, huh?
It's perfect, thank you all.
I love it!
[gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
Wow.
I'm actually really happy.
Hm?
Hey, look who decided
to join us.
Yeah, yeah.
[sighs]
Didn't get ya anything.
Didn't borrow a towel anyway.
Fine with me.
[gasps]
[UKA]
Am I allowed to be this lucky?
When do I get hit
by a bolt of lightning?
-Hey, Ishimori!
-[UKA] What's up?
[ASUMI] I took a pic
of that "sky heart"
you found yesterday,
and it's gotten over
three hundred likes!
[YURU] [gasps]
That's so cool!
[ASUMI] Yeah!
Maybe just a little scary.
Three hundred people liked it?
Wait, you're gonna love this!
[ASUMI]
Huh? Who's that?
[YUKINO]
You know that guy?
Dang, he's a hottie!
Who is that, anyway?
Seriously?
This is Kai, guys.
[all gasping]
Yeah, not joking.
[ASUMI] Miura, you've gotta
rock the black hair again!
-Is that from your yearbook?
-[YURU] Yep.
-Bring the book with you!
-[YURU] Uh-uh.
-[ASUMI] Why not?
-I wanna see it, too!
[YURU]
Hmm, well...
I'll show you mine
if you show me yours.
[UKA] [gasps]
My old yearbook.
You, too, Ishimori!
We'd love to see your
yearbook from junior high!
[UKA]
Huh?
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND 1B]
"Stony?"
That's the nickname everyone
called her in junior high.
[REMI] And all she does
is stare at people
with a blank face.
There's no better name!
Not for a freak like that!
-[ASUMI] Oh, sorry if, uh--
-[YURU] Like, "Sorry" for what?
[ASUMI] No, I mean, no pressure
if you'd rather not.
[UKA] [chuckles]
Yeah.
Uh, thank you.
Just spaced a little.
[GROUP]
Hmm?
♪
[groaning]
[UKA]
Let's see.
[thuds]
[grunts]
[UKA]
Huh?
There it is.
I'm sorta happy
I could still find it,
and sorta not.
♪
I've never opened it.
I was too scared
of what I might find inside.
[whimpering]
♪
Good. It's safe.
I'm normal.
I was worried
my face would look weird,
or maybe I blinked,
or something.
But it's okay.
I can show them.
There's nothing too bad.
[YURU]
I've got the goods!
I'm so ugly here!
You kidding?
You look great!
Ooh, this girl's from Class C!
-Oh.
-[ASUMI] Yeah!
-[ASUMI] Ah, this guy's cute!
-[YUKINO] Taken, I'm afraid.
[ASUMI]
Ugh!
And here we have
West Junior High!
Ooh! Let me see!
[YUKINO]
Wow, is that Takamine?
-[ASUMI] Seto's here, too!
-[YUKINO] And that's Ayumi!
[UKA] [whimpering]
She looks adorable!
You were all in the same class?
[MIRU]
Whoa, we got a hottie alert!
[YURU]
Uh, who?
[MIRU]
That one. Serina Kanno!
[ASUMI]
Holy crap, she's gorgeous!
-[ASUMI] Is she famous?
-[YURU] She is to us!
[UKA]
She's so pretty.
And Miura shared
a class with her.
[YURU]
The boys were obsessed!
And she's a total sweetheart!
[MIRU] Meanwhile, Kai's
looking stiff as a board.
[YURU]
Least he's consistent, though.
Boy does not smile.
[ASUMI] Oh, I've got a few
from the field trip!
Wait, I have one
from Field Day.
[MIRU]
Was this a party?
[UKA] Yesterday, they all
avoided mentioning my past.
I shouldn't force it on them.
That's stupid.
Honestly, it was silly.
Why would I think it would help
me be a part of the group?
Hold on, she's leaving?
[UKA]
I'm so embarrassed.
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs]
[UKA]
It's just too much for me.
I can't let other people
see my past.
I'll lock it up back home.
Of course...
I wish I could lock up
the memories with it.
[gasps]
You're here?
-So, where are you?
-Hold on!
Hey, g-give that
give that back to me!
-Just answer.
-Um?
I was Class Four.
-You look good here.
-Huh!
[KAI]
I figured since you ran away,
it must've been a bad photo.
Nothing like that.
I didn't have any
good memories.
And there were no fun stories
I could share with them.
-So what?
-Huh?
What?
You heard me.
-So, I want to forget it.
-[KAI] Why?
Ah?
Because it hurts?
That's why you can't forget.
That pain turned you
into the person you are.
And the person you are
is more than enough.
Our whole class found
that out yesterday.
[gasps]
♪
[wind rustling]
Do you mind
if I show them this one?
It's kinda funny.
[UKA]
Huh!
Hmm.
Let me do it!
♪
[sighs]
[KAI]
Add it to the pile.
But I didn't lend you
anything yesterday.
♪
[KAI]
You still deserve it.
[chuckles softly]
♪
[UKA]
He's got a point.
I'll be fine.
I'll make new memories here.
With them!
It'll be easy!
[indistinct chatter]
-[TOMOYA] Hey, Uka?
-Huh?
Have a second to chat?
-Sure.
-[TOMOYA] Go on.
Uhh...I'm sorry about before.
You know the messed up
sign on our hike?
-[TOMOYA] That was her.
-Huh!
You really did that?
But why?
You've just gotten
so close to Kai.
It's possible
I overreacted a bit
and let my jealousy
get the best of me.
But it's outta my system
and I won't do it again.
-Bye.
-Ah!
[sighs]
Sorry.
No, it's fine.
I don't know
where she got the idea
that I'm close with him.
[sighs]
Have you legitimately
not caught on yet?
Huh?
You remember
what I told you before?
How Kai can be
awkward sometimes,
since he barely
ever talks to girls?
Neither of you realize
how close you are.
At least, how close
you look to everyone else.
[TOMOYA]
It's fine.
Just something you should know,
'cause I'm sure
other girls think the same.
You say he changed you, right?
But how do you really know your
life is better with him in it?
[UKA]
I mean...
[TOMOYA]
I'm not sure.
You might've been
happier without him.
It's great he managed
to pull you
out of the pit you were in.
But on the other hand,
you've gotten into trouble
just because you're near him.
Almost like a target's been
placed on your back.
[whimpering]
Let me ask you this.
Are you truly making
any progress here?
[TOMOYA]
Or is it possible,
you're still the same person
you've always been?
If you want to live
a happier life than before...
should you be next to Kai?
[UKA]
How am I supposed to take that?
Because to me, it sounds like
he's saying I shouldn't
even be here.
That I don't belong at all.
Do I...Miura?
[YASUSHI]
Yo, Kai.
Is it true that you
and Serina Kanno
went out in junior high?
-[KUMIKO] She's your ex?
-Who's she?
Is that for real?
Just shut up already.
-[YASUSHI] That's not a no!
-[gasps]
-[UNDERCUT] Crazy.
-[YASUSHI] That’s wild.
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA] I thought
maybe if I chased him,
I could slowly get closer.
[UKA]
But there’s no chance.
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
I just happen to be near him,
but I'm still all alone.
[coughs] I'm trying
so hard to catch up,
but the distance
is only growing.
[beeping]
[UKA'S MOM]
Let's take a look.
Good! It's come down
a lot since yesterday!
Don't overwork yourself
when you're back at school.
I'll go get some fruit for you.
♪
[UKA] I wound up
coming down with a cold.
I have to get better fast.
The longer I'm out of school,
the more I'll make people
worry about me.
♪
[sighs]
-[door opens]
-[UKA'S MOM] Uka, guess what?
Your friend's calling!
A nice girl named "Ayumi!"
[whimpering]
-Here you go!
-Thank you.
Hi, uh, Ayumi.
Are you there?
[KAI]
No, it's me.
Smooth move, dude.
Kai, don't take
my phone like that!
-How ya holdin' up?
-[whimpering]
[KAI]
You there?
[rumbling]
[UKA] What?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I wasn't ready!
That was his voice.
♪
I'm sorry.
Am I talking to Miura?
[KAI]
You got it.
Ayumi's here.
She wanted to know
what you're up to today.
Think she was hoping
to hang out.
-[coughs]
-That sounds like a no.
Can't, if ya got a cold.
[UKA]
No, I'm not that bad.
[coughs]
[KAI]
So, you coming, then?
[AYUMI] What?
That's awful.
I didn't know you were sick!
[KAI]
Well...I'd rather
you stayed home
if you're sick.
Sorry, I can't go.
It's okay!
Just get well quickly!
[gasps]
Thanks!
-See ya.
-[AYUMI] Need anything?
[UKA]
Uh, no!
But I am really happy
to hear from you all
while I'm out sick!
Please tell Ayumi
I said so, too!
[TOMOYA]
Hm.
[KAI] Oh, I meant to ask.
Which way to the train station?
-Huh?
-[KAI] From your place.
Oh, uh...right.
♪
[UKA]
"My place?"
Wait a second.
[sighs]
There she is! Uka!
You okay?
[AYUMI]
Sorry to show up uninvited!
Good to see ya, though!
Lookin' good!
[chuckles]
Hey, want us
to get you anything?
[KAI] I'll see you,
tomorrow, yeah?
♪
[laughs]
Let's do something fun
when you're better!
[UKA]
Okay.
Sure.
Yeah!
♪
[birds chirping]
Listen up, I've got some photos
from the field trip here!
-[ASUMI] For real?
-[YURU] Let us see!
[ABE] I'm making copies,
so write your names
on the ones you want.
[indistinct chatter]
[SHIRAISHI]
Check it.
I guess Ishimori's
not big on posing?
Like she's haunting
the mountain!
Of course, Kai's expressionless
in every one.
[KIYOSHI]
Are you surprised?
[YASUSHI] Hold up.
He's smiling in some over here!
[KIYOSHI]
Whoa, he is!
Wait, Ishimori's next
to him in all of 'em!
[TONBO]
Holy crap!
-[TONBO] You go, Ishimori!
-It's true!
You've seen how Kai
smiles when you're there.
-Huh?
-Haven't you?
Huh?
[whimpering]
You really didn't notice?
Ah!
Wait...I get it now!
[AYUMI]
Oh! Oh, my gosh!
You've got a crush on him!
Well, you've got
a wingwoman here!
Though you're not making it
very easy on yourself, are you?
[chuckles]
I'm aware.
[UKA] I've got a friend
I can talk with about anything,
and a boy I like.
[SATORU] [chuckles]
Check it out!
We've got the rare "Kai smile."
[sighs]
Hmm?
[SATORU] And Ishimori's got
a lot of good ones, too!
They're fine.
Her smile's
got something to it.
[SATORU]
How so?
It's honestly kinda cute.
[gasps] There's something
I thought I'd never see!
♪
[UKA] No matter
what anyone says, I'm staying.
I'm supposed to be here.
Even if I can't
close the distance
and nothing changes,
here, the world is bright!
[water trickling]
[creaking]
Okay, shake it off.
[footfall]
-[Serina screaming]
-What the...
[whimpering]
Huh?
[SERINA] Ah, I'm so sorry!
Did it hit you?
Oh, uh, no!
[SERINA]
Oh, thank goodness!
And I so appreciate
you catching it!
[sighs]
[UKA] Whatever happens
with all of this,
I'll accept it.
What's taking so long, Serina?
Thanks again!
[UKA]
No matter what.
TO BE CONTINUED